Guide to the James R. Houck papers.
Houck, James R. papers.
- Series IV. Shuttle Infrared Telescope Facility (SIRTF)
  - Multiband Imaging Photometer Information Packets, 1989-1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - HEAO Management Plan, Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Operations Memorandums, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Transparencies: IRS Optical Concept, 1990-10-24 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Optics Papers, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Optics Papers, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Pointing Facility Documents, 1988-1996 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Spider Diffraction Analysis, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Straylight Paper, 1990-10-17 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Tertiary Facility (Tiger Team) Information, 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Vibration Levels for SIRTF Memorandum, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Papers Concerning SIRTF, 1987-1991 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Papers Concerning Radiation, 1979-1990 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Presentation Packets, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Status Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Photographs- KP 3.39, 1971-07 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Notes and Transparencies, Undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Photographs- 4.178 and 4.84, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Photographs- 4.004-3, 1970-11 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Photographs- 4.177, 1968-02 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Photographs- KP 3.40 (Recovery Operation), 1972 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Photographs-4.312 (Aerobee NASA), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Stepping Motor Control Diagrams, 1978-03 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Stepping Motor Control Diagrams, 1973-04 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Mt. Pleasant Electronic Documents, Undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Diagrams, Undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Blueprints, Undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - A31.320-2 Si:As Electronics Rocket Diagrams, Undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - A04.004-3 Connector Layout Diagrams, 1970-05-06 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - SIRTF Appendix A, 1978-04-14 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    Focal Plane Instruments and Requirements Science Team
  - SIRTF Summary Documents, 1979-08 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - SIRTF Multiple Instrument Chamber Reconfiguration Study, 1991-05 (Box 14)
    University of Rochester Department of Physics and Astronomy
  - SIRTF Multiple Instrument Chamber Concept Definition Study, 1989-09-13 (Box 14)
    NASA Ames Research Center
  - Multiband Imaging Photometer for SIRTF Document, 1991-04-17 (Box 14)
  - Multiband Imaging Photometer for SIRTF Description, 1991-05-22 (Box 14)
  - SIRTF Report of the Focal Plane Instruments and Requirements Science Team and the SIRTF Science Working Group, 1979-11 (Box 14)
  - NIRFOS (A Near Infrared Faint Object Spectrometer) St. Missions Technical Proposal, Undated (Box 14)
  - SIRTF Science Instrument Interface Description, 1983-04 (Box 14)
  - The SIRTF Concept and its Realization (Box 14)
  - Final Report SIRTF Shared Focal Plane Tiger Team, 1990-11 (Box 14)
  - Proceedings of the 1991 North American Workshop on Infrared Spectroscopy, 1991-06-28 (Box 14)
  - SIRTF Documents and Summaries, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - NASA Contract Report 177380: SIRTF Telescope Instrument Changeout and Cryogen Replenishment Study, 1985-08 (Box 15)
  - SIRTF Radiation Effects Analysis Reports, 1975-12 (Box 15)
  - Requirement Analysis, Undated (Box 15)
  - Design Study for SIRTF Volume 3.4, 1974-04 (Box 15)
  - Design Study for SIRTF Volume 3.1, 1974-04 (Box 15)
  - Payload/Orbiter Contamination Control Requirement Study NAS8-30452, 1974-05 (Box 15)
  - NASA Contractor Report 166614: Study of Alternate Optical and Fine Guidance Sensor Designs for the SIRTF, 1984-11 (Box 15)
  - NASA Contractor Report 166612: Pointing and Control System Design Study for the SIRTF, 1984-11 (Box 15)
  - NASA Contractor Report 166613: Thermal and Cryogenic Study for the SIRTF, 1984-11 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - SIRTF Phase A Concept Description Ames Research Center, 1981-08-28 (Box 15)
  - A Stellar/Planetary Infrared Echelle Spectroradiometer [SPIRES], 2000 (Box 15)
  - Working Group Meeting Materials, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Working Group Meeting Materials, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Working Group Meeting Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Appendices 1-6 for SIRTF, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Appendices 7-8 for SIRTF, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Appendices 9-12 for SIRTF, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Committee Report and Meeting #13, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Appendices B-F for SIRTF, Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Appendices G-K for SIRTF, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Progress Report and Meeting Report, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 17th SIRTF Working Group Meeting Material, 1989-7-1989-12 (Box 21)
  - NASA-SIRTF Documents (1), 1989 (Box 21)
  - SIRTF Working Group Kickoff Meeting, 1990-10-1990-12 (Box 21)
  - NASA-SIRTF Documents (2), 1989-09-15 (Box 21)
  - SIRTF IR Array Camera Working Group Meeting, 1993-04-21-1993-04-23 (Box 21)
  - 16th SIRTF Working Group Meeting Materials, 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - 19th SIRTF Working Group Meeting Materials, 1990-05-14-1990-04-16 (Box 22)
  - SIRTF Working Group Meeting and Cost Estimate Materials, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Computer Code, 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - SIRTF Working Group Minutes, 1995 (Box 22)
  - SIRTF Working Group Meeting Materials, 1992-03-16-1992-03-18 (Box 22)
  - SIRTF Working Group Payload Workshop, 1992-12-01-1992-12-03 (Box 22)
  - IRS Information Review, Integration, and Testing, 1992-07-27-1992-09-26 (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous Meeting Materials, 1992-06-1993-08 (Box 22)
  - Jim Houck SIRTF Transparencies, Undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - SIRTF, IRS, and MPR's Progress Reports, 1986-11-1987-11 (Box 24)
  - SIRTF, IRS, and MPR's Progress Reports, 1987-12-1988-08 (Box 24)
  - SIRTF, IRS, and MPR's Progress Reports, 1988-09-1989-02 (Box 24)
  - SIRTF, IRS, and MPR's Progress Reports, 1989-03-1989-04 (Box 24)
  - SIRTF, IRS, and MPR's Progress Reports, 1989-05-1989-11 (Box 24)
  - SIRTF, IRS, and MPR's Progress Reports, 1989-12-1990-10 (Box 24)
  - SIRTF, IRS, and MPR's Progress Reports, 1990-11-1992-09 (Box 25)
  - SIRTF Phase A Study Bimonthly Progress Reports, 1994-10-01-1996-01-31 (Box 25)
  - SIRTF Progress Reports, 1993-07-1994-09 (Box 25)
  - SIRTF Proposals, 1984-10-01-1995-09-30 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - SIRTF Proposals, 1985-10-01-1988-09-30 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - SIRTF System Engineering Report, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Mechanisms for SIRTF, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Baseline Telescope Reports, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Coolers for SIRTF Report, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - SIRTF Working Group, 1984-12 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - SIRTF Spectrometer Report, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Mechanism Notes, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Encoder Problem Notes, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Infrared Spectrometer Optical Design, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - SIRTF Working Group, 1992-12 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Charts and Transparencies, 1988-11 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - SIRTF Working Group, 1990-05 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Infrared Spectrometer Status, 1991-03-12 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Kick-off Meetings, 1986-1990 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Pellegrin Meetings Materials, 1986-1988 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Washington SIRTF Working Group, 1987-06 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - IRR Vugraphs, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - IRS Technology Review, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Ball Labs Materials, 1985-01-11 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - IRS Correspondence, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - SpectroCam-10 Progress Reports, 1991-03 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous SIRTF Materials, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - SIRTF Telemail, 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - SIRTF Instrument Summary, Undated (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Schedules, 1985-1991 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - IRS Meetings, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Phase B Proposal, 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Implementation Plan, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Edison Infrared Space Observatory Materials, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - SIRTF Materials, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - IRS Materials- Ithaca, 1993-08 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Payload Presentation, 1993-08-10 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Sensitivity and Dynamics Presentation, 1993-08-12 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Bloomfield Presentation, 1993-11-05 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - SIRTF Peer Review, 1994-02-14 (Box 36)
  - SIRTF Presentations, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - SIRTF Mission Concept, 1993-10 (Box 36)
  - Astrophyics Subcommittee, 1994-02-1994-11 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Detectors Presentation, 1992-12 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - IRS Schedule, 1991-07 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - DITS Materials, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Ball Mechanism Study, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Pamphlets, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - FUSE Presentation, Undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - SIRTF Pre-Proposal Documents, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Grant Proposals for SIRTF, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - SIRTF Correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Grant Proposal for SIRTF, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Systems Reports, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Ball Labs Input for SIRTF, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - SIRTF Budgets, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Misc. SIRTF Proposals, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Misc. Meeting Materials, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Misc. Meeting Materials, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Washington Meeting Materials, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Misc. Documentation, Undated (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Misc. Documentation- Echelle and Backgrounds, Undated (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Misc. Photos- Astro-2 UV and LEAR, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - C-141 Photos, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - SIRTF Photos, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Misc. Viewgraphs, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Misc. Talk Materials, 1983-1985 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Fine Structure Lines Materials, Undated (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - KAO Transparencies, Undated (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Pellerin Brief Materials, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Artwork- C141 and LEAR Jet, Undated (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - NASA Headquarters Notes, 1986-09-08 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Optics: LEAR and C-141 and Lab, Undated (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Ball Labs and Capps Review V.G. Materials, 1990-06 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Technology Review, 1984-06 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - CSAA Meeting Materials, 1983-03 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Optical AstroTech Materials, Undated (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - SIRTF Figures, Undated (Box 41, Folder 38)
    Note on folder: Figures needing modification
  - Hawaii Background Materials, Undated (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - C-141 Proposal Figures, 1976-1979 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Infrared Group Notes, Undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Materials, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Deglitcher Figures, Undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - C-141 Science V.G. Materials, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - IRS (Infrared Spectrograph) Introduction Materials, 1991-03-21 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Notes - SSPM and BIB's, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - SIRTF Detector Reports, 1979-1987 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - SIRTF Detector Reports, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - SIRTF Talk, Undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Technology Review, 1986-05-01 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Misc. Papers- BIB's, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Ball Labs Optics Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Background Viewgraphs, Undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Ball Labs Progress Reports, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Board Meetings Materials, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Series V. NASAmail
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1993-11-01-1994-03-31 (Box 15)
  - SIRTF E-mail, 1994-04-01-1994-09-30 (Box 15)
  - SIRTF E-mail, 1994-12-01-1995-07-31 (Box 16)
  - SIRTF E-mail, 1995-08-01-1996-04-30 (Box 16)
  - SIRTF E-mail, 1996-04-03-1996-10-18 (Box 16)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1991-01-01-1991-02-28 (Box 16)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1991-01-17-1991-03-08 (Box 16)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1991-03-01-1991-05-15 (Box 16)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1991-05-15-1991-07-31 (Box 17)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1991-07-24-1991-11-26 (Box 17)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1991-10-01-1991-12-31 (Box 17)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1991-12-03-1992-02-10 (Box 17)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1992-01-01-1992-04-30 (Box 17)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1992-02-11-1992-05-22 (Box 17)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1992-05-01-1992-12-31 (Box 17)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1993-01-01-1993-10-31 (Box 18)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1993-02-04-1993-06-14 (Box 18)
  - SIRTF Telemail, 1993-06-01-1993-10-12 (Box 18)
  - SIRTF Telemail, 1993-10-13-1993-12-31 (Box 18)
  - SIRTF Telemail, 1992-10-20-1993-02-04 (Box 18)
  - SIRTF Telemail, 1992-05-22-1992-11-30 (Box 18)
  - SIRTF Telemail, 1994-01-01-1994-03-18 (Box 18)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1994-08-04 (Box 19)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1994-05-03-1995-07-31 (Box 19)
  - SIRTF E-mail, 1994-10-03-1994-09-29 (Box 19)
  - SIRTF E-mail, 1996-10-21-1997-02-28 (Box 19)
  - SIRTF E-mail, 1997-03-01-1997-05-31 (Box 19)
  - SIRTF E-mail, 1997-06-01-1997-09-15 (Box 19)
  - SIRTF E-mail, 1997-09-16-1998-01-15 (Box 19)
  - SIRTF E-mail, 1998-01-16-1998-06-19 (Box 20)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1990-02-26-1990-07-12 (Box 20)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1990-10-15-1990-01-16 (Box 20)
  - SIRTF Telemail, 1987-09-14-1988-09-15 (Box 20)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1991-03-08-1991-04-30 (Box 20)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1991-05-01-1991-07-23 (Box 20)
  - SIRTF Telemail, 1988-09-01-1989-10-02 (Box 20)
  - SIRTF Telemail, 1988-09-16-1989-03-20 (Box 21)
  - SIRTF Telemail, 1989-09-13-1990-03-14 (Box 21)
  - SIRTF NASAmail, 1990-07-16-1990-10-16 (Box 21)
  - MIMAS Email, 1997-07-24-1998-01-05 (Box 21)
- Series VI. IRS (Infrared Spectrometer)
  - SIRTF and IRS End Item Data Package Pt 1, 2000-03-09 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - SIRTF and IRS End Item Data Package Pt 2, 2000-03-09 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - SIRTF and IRS End Item Data Package Pt 3, 2000-03-09 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - SIRTF and IRS End Item Data Package Pt 4, 2000-03-09 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - SIRTF and IRS End Item Data Package for Software Pt 1, 2000-03-09 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - SIRTF and IRS End Item Data Package for Software Pt 2, 2000-03-09 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - SIRTF and IRS End Item Data Package for the Combined Electronics 2, 2000-03-09 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - SIRTF and IRS End Item Data Package for the Cold Assembly, 2000-03-09 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - IRS Filter Curves Data Package, 1999-02-17-1999-02-19 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - IRS Reference Book, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - IRS Peak-up (Simgen 1) Charts, Undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - IRS Peak-up (Simgen 2) Charts, 1998-2000 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - IRS As-Run "Ad Hoc" Test Procedures, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - IRS Reduction Plan II (and test notes), 2000-2003 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - IRS Data Reduction Plan I (Functional and Ad-Hoc), 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - SIRTF Critical Design Review of the Si:As and Si:Sb Focal Plane Mount Assemblies (FPMAs) for IRS/MIPS, 1997-08-18 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Ass Covering Documents, Part 1: Left Buttock (Not kidding), 2002 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Request for Proposal for SIRTF Industry Team Members, 1996-01-09 (Box 23)
  - SIRTF Test Plans, 1997-1999 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - IRS As-Run Functional Test Procedures Pt 1, 2000-2002 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - IRS As-Rum Functional Test Procedures Pt 2, 2000-2002 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Gemini Documents, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Gemini Documents, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - IRS Optics Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - IRS Mechanisms Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - IRS Cryogenics Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 2004 Spitzer/IRS Science Fest at Cornell, 2004-12-06 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - GTO Review and Planning Meeting, 2005-06-14-2005-06-16 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - IRS Pipeline Review (S6), 2001-09-07 (Box 24)
  - IRS Pipeline Review (S5), 2001-09-15 (Box 24)
  - SIRTF Preliminary Design Review of the Si:As and Si:Sb Focal Plane Mount Assemblies for IRS/MIPS, 1997-02-25 (Box 24)
  - SIRTF Preliminary Non-Advocate Review, 1996-06-26-1996-06-27 (Box 24)
  - Gemini US Science Advisory Committee, 1994-10-13-1994-10-14 (Box 24)
  - Requisition Request Form: A56-4100, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Requisition Request Form: U25-4303, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Requisition Request Form: U25-8507, 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Requisition Request Form: U25-8479, 1985-1988 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Requisition Request Form: U25-8458, 1982-1983 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Requisition Request Form: U25-8457, Undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Requisition Request Form: U25-8513, 1984-1986 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Requisition Request Form: A56-4300, 1984-1985 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Requisition Request Form: U25, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Requisition Request Form: U25, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Requisition Request Form: A56, 1988-1990 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Annual Reports, 1985-1991 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports: Steven Beckwith, 1980-1989 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Annual Reports: James Houck, 1980-1992 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Duclos Travel Forms, 1988-1991 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Student Travel Forms, 1988-1990 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Herter Travel Forms, 1988-1990 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Beckwith Travel Forms, 1988-1991 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Other Travellers Forms, 1989-1991 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Houck Travel Forms, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Houck Travel Forms, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Houck Travel Forms, 1991-01-1991-08 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Houck Travel Forms, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Houck Travel Forms, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Invoices, 1990-10-1992-12 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Discount Invoices, 1990-09-1992-10 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Employee Applications, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Hartung-Boothroyd Observatory, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Telescopes Documents, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Course Evaluation Forms, 1984-1987 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Astronomy 215 Forms, 1983-1984 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Astronomy 101+201 Forms, 1986-1989 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Astronomy 102+104 Forms, 1986-1990 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Rocket-Infrared Observations of the Galactic Center- Soifer+Houck, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Rocket-Infrared Observations of the Interplanetary Medium Soifer et al, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Rocket-Borne Liquid Helium Cooled Telescope Harwit et al, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Yoga, Science + Spirituality Brochures, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - 20 to 40 Micron Spectroscopy of the Orion Nebula, Houck et al, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Jupiter: Its Infrared Spectrum from 16 to 40 Micrometers: Houck et al, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Spectrophotometry of OH 26.5+0.6 from 2 to 40 Microns; Forrest et al, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - 1 Millimeter Continuum Observations of Extragalactic Objects, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Misc. Forms, 1988-1991 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Series VII. IRAS (Infrared Astronomy Satellite)
  - IRAF User Handbook Vol 1, 1986-1989 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - IRAF User Handbook Vol 1-2, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - IRAF User Handbook Vol 1A, 1986-1992 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - IRAS (Infrared Astronomy Satellite) Memoranda, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - IRAS Proposals, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Documents Concerning IRAS Contamination, 1977-1982 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Documents Concerning IRAS Contamination, 1978-1982 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - IRAS Reports and Proposals, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Total Flux Measurements, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - IRAS Data Analysis, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - General Technical Notes (IRAS), 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - IRAS Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Experiment Documentation, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - IRAS Action Item Lists, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Deep Sky Survey and Operations, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Sky Coverage, Reliability, and Completeness Documentation, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Joint Project Requirements for IRAS, 1977-07 (Box 26)
  - IOC(?) Test Materials, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - IOC(?) Test Materials, 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - IRAS Progress Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - IRAS Slitless Spectrograph Materials, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Project Plan for IRAS Execution Phase, 1979-02 (Box 27)
  - IRAS Analysis of the Transmittance of Off-Axis Energy Due to Scattering and Diffraction, 1978-06-30-1979-09-21 (Box 27)
  - IRAS Analysis of the Transmittance of Off-Axis Energy Due to Scattering and Diffraction, 1978-06-30 (Box 27)
  - Joint Project Requirements for IRAS, 1979-02 (Box 27)
  - IRAS End of Mission Report, Undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - The IRAS Radiation Environment, 1978-12 (Box 27)
  - Performance Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - IRAS In-Orbit Performance Assessment, 1983-06-21 (Box 27)
  - IRAS Pre-Shipment Review, 1982-11-26-1982-11-27 (Box 27)
  - IRAS Joint Project Requirements, 1981-03 (Box 27)
  - Proposal for Telescope System for IRAS Vol 1, Book 1, 1977-03-01 (Box 27)
  - IRAS Scientific Analysis System Function Description Document, 1982-08-13 (Box 27)
  - Scientific Data Analysis System: Database Management Subsystem User's Guide, 1980-09-30 (Box 27)
  - IRAS Scientific Analysis System Function Description Document, 1981-09-18 (Box 27)
  - IRAS Telescope Performance Requirements, 1982-06 (Box 27)
  - IRAS Focal Plane Assembly Design Review, 1978-03-16-1978-03-17 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Scientific Data Analysis System Skyflux Subsystem User's Guide, 1982-08-27 (Box 27)
  - IRAS/TSY Critical Design Review, 1978-12-13-1978-12-15 (Box 27)
  - IRAS/TSY Critical Design Review, 1978-12-13-1978-12-15 (Box 27)
  - IRAS/TSY Critical Design Review, 1978-12-13-1978-12-15 (Box 27)
  - Detector Report Materials, 1979-1982 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Tests and Diagrams, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Preliminary Test Reports, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Final Detector Reports, 1979-1982 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Notes and Computer Code, 1978-1980 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Noise Data, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Field-Effect Transistor Papers, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - IRAS Flight Notes, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Analog I/O Board Documentation, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - IRAS Detector Tests, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - IRAS Resistor Tests, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Wire Instrument Technical Concept Review, 1994-05-19-1994-05-20 (Box 28)
  - Wire Science and Mission Technical Concept Review, 1994-05-19-1994-05-20 (Box 28)
  - A Proposal for the Small Explorer Missions Program Wide-Field Infrared Explorer (WIRE) Section 1: Investigation and Technical Plan, 1993-01-12 (Box 28)
  - WIRE (Wide Field Infrared Explorer) Information, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - WIRE (Wide Field Infrared Explorer) Information, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Overhead Transparencies for Jay M. Pasachoff's Astronomy: From the Earth to the Universe, 4th edition, Undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - IRAS/TSY(Telescope System?) Critical Design Review, 1978-12-13-1978-12-15 (Box 28)
  - IRAS/TSY(Telescope System?) Critical Design Review, 1978-12-13-1978-12-15 (Box 28)
  - IRAS/TSY(Telescope System?) Critical Design Review, 1978-12-13-1978-12-15 (Box 28)
  - IRAS Mission Reports, Undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Joint Project Requirements for IRAS, 1978-10 (Box 28)
  - Infra-Red Experiment (IRAS), 1976-03 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Experiment Definition Study for the IRAS, 1976-03 (Box 28)
  - Preliminary Reports for IRAS, 1975-12 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Reports for IRAS, 1974-10-1976-05 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Final Report: Design, Manufacturing, and Testing of the Flight Unit Dax Low Resolution Spectrometer and Photometers, 1980-06-26 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - IRAS Dutch Additional Experiment Description, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - IRAS Project Description, 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Workshop Proceedings, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Straylight in the IRAS, 1982-05 (Box 29)